[{"question": " there&#146;s this woman, that i like. a lot. well, it&#146;s complicated. she&#146;s with this other guy. for a long time. and i could never do that to the guy, y&#146;know? &#146;ccause we&#146;re really good friends.", "answer": " so, uh, this guy, she used to go out with, is, uh&#133; is he a good guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " yeah, he&#146;s the best.", "answer": " then talk to him! he might be fine with it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " oh, i don&#146;t know.", "answer": " joey, it&#146;s worth finding out. i mean, if you really like her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i do! so much! i can&#146;t stop thinking about her! i can&#146;t sleep, i&#151;", "answer": " okay, joey, you know what? you have to go for it. how often does this happen to you, huh? you owe it to yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  did you um&#151;i&#146;m sorry, did you just say it&#146;s rachel?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " um, you&#133;you like rachel?", "answer": " yes. i like rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " rachel?!", "answer": "  yeah, okay but look, buy uh&#151;hey-hey, y&#146;know, y&#146;know who else i like? you! and it-it doesn&#146;t get said enough. i like you ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " but r-r-rachel-rachel?!", "answer": " yeah, but it&#146;s not a big deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " it&#146;s not a big deal? oh, i&#146;m sorry i just&#133;um, i&#133;what about all the stuff you-you just said? i mean how about, i like&#151;you-you can&#146;t stop thinking about her. like how you can&#146;t sleep?", "answer": " i&#146;m an actor, y&#146;know? as-as a group, we tend to be over dramatic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " rachel who&#146;s carrying my baby? rachel?", "answer": " look no, i-i know it&#146;s bad, and i know it&#146;s wrong. okay? but-but it&#146;s not like anything&#146;s ever gonna happen. y&#146;know? these-these are just feelings, they&#146;re gonna go away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " oh come on ross! hey ross-ross don&#146;t&#133;", "answer": "  i just&#151;y&#146;know&#151;i-i just have one&#151;rachel?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh-oh! okay, she&#146;s kicking!", "answer": " oh!  she&#146;s growing inside you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " whoa!!", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " wow that was a big one.", "answer": " i think that&#146;s the youngest girl ever to reject me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  oh hey you guys!", "answer": " oh hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey listen let me ask you, do you believe in soul mates?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh yes i do. i do. i believe that there is one perfect person out there for everyone. and do you know how you find him? you stop looking for him. that&#146;s why i stopped looking for russell crowe. he&#146;ll find me.", "answer": " uh-huh,  and you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " no. i mean i believe that uh, certain people are more suited for each other and i believe in falling in love, but soul mates, i don&#146;t think they exist.", "answer": " okay, good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " well last night, i met monica&#146;s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " yeah, i had a date with this guy, and i swear to god, he is her other half.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  well, what&#146;s he like?!", "answer": " well he&#146;s tall.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " he has brown hair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " of course, of course.", "answer": " a tall guy with hair similar to mine, oh unknowable universe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " he works with food!", "answer": " oh sure. older?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " obviously, and he&#146;s british.", "answer": " oh, i was just gonna ask!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " yeah? and, he&#146;s-he&#146;s so centered and mature and confident.", "answer": " oh, it&#146;s so sad they never had a chance to meet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " luckily, the guy she settled for can&#146;t hear what you&#146;re talking about.", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m so sorry. um, and maybe i&#146;m wrong! i but&#151;y&#146;know i&#146;m gonna go out with him again, i&#146;ll find out more.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " you believe that this guy is destined for someone else and you&#146;re still gonna date him?", "answer": " well, he may not be my soul mate, but a girl&#146;s gotta eat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i just talked to joey, i just&#151;i want to see how you were.", "answer": " oh y&#146;know, i still&#151;i can&#146;t believe it. joey and rachel i mean it&#146;s&#133; it&#146;s like you and me going out, only weirder!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " all right, i know you&#146;re hurting, and-and i want to be supportive, but don&#146;t say that again.", "answer": " oh my god! what if, what if they get married? then he&#146;d be the stepfather of my child.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " honey, i don&#146;t think that&#146;s something we need to worry about! first of all he&#146;s-he&#146;s never gonna tell her how he feels about her. and even if he did you have no idea how she&#146;d react.", "answer": " sure, because women never like joey. y&#146;know, i think he&#146;s a virgin.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " joey&#133;he&#146;s not even thinking about going after rachel!", "answer": " he&#146;s not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " no! all he&#146;s thinking about is how you&#146;re taking this! i mean, listen it&#146;s totally freaking him out. he&#146;s talking about moving to vermont.", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " he says he wants to leave the country.  he thinks you hate him.", "answer": " hate him? i&#133; no, i don&#146;t hate him.  it&#146;s just it&#146;s rachel, y&#146;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " honey i can&#146;t even imagine how hard this must be for you. but, i don&#146;t want you to lose joey over it. and right now he just needs to know that you&#146;re still his friend.", "answer": " okay. okay, i&#146;ll talk to him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh! hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " umm, chandler, monica, this is don.", "answer": " oh, hello.  hello.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  soul mate.", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  soul mate.", "answer": " so, what have you guys been doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " well, we just had a terrible lunch today at reattica. what is with all the sun-dried tomatoes at that place?", "answer": " i know! what is this, 1985?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " that&#146;s exactly what i said. phoebe, isn&#146;t that strange.", "answer": " not really.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " what&#146;s wrong with sun-dried tomatoes?  on a barbecue chicken pizza?  no?", "answer": " so don, what-what other restaurants do you like?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " well, octavio, 27&amp;7&#151;oh! and there&#146;s this great little place, alessandro&#146;s.", "answer": " oh my god! that&#146;s my restaurant, i&#146;m the chef there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " you&#146;re kidding me!", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " your food is fantastic! wow, i really want to talk to you about your menu, once i get some coffees first. um, anyone want any?", "answer": " oh, i&#146;d like a latte. oh y&#146;know what? if you&#146;re gonna talk about me, i&#146;m gonna go with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " what are you doing?!", "answer": " nothing! i swear to god i didn&#146;t know you guys would be here! and the good news is you didn&#146;t believe in soul mates. so&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i believe in tall, handsome strangers who hit on my wife!", "answer": " they&#146;re just talking, and y&#146;know what? just because i think they&#146;re soul mates doesn&#146;t mean anything&#146;s gonna happen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  phoebe, good work.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " look, i understand if you came by to hit me, i deserve it.", "answer": " no, i don&#146;t want to hit you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " oh what then? kick me?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  bite me?", "answer": " no, no i don&#146;t want to do anything to you. all right? i just want to tell you that i&#146;m not mad at you and&#133;and that i certainly do not hate you. i just, i just came here to say that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " oh now&#151;hey ross-ross! do you wanna-wanna come in for a beer or something?", "answer": " uh&#133;yeah sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " do uh, do you got any beer? all-all i got is this melon stuff that rachel left. i don&#146;t&#133;", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " anyway, it uh&#133;look it&#146;ll just&#133;take me a while to get over her, that&#146;s all. i&#146;m not even sure how to do that, i mean i&#146;ve never been in love before so&#133;", "answer": " what?! you&#146;re in love with her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah, i thought you knew that.", "answer": " umm, no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " i think you need to tell her how you feel.", "answer": " okay that&#146;s the green stuff talkin&#146;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " no, i&#146;m serious. you-you need to find out where she is, because if she&#146;s not where you are, then you can start to move past this.", "answer": " but what if uh&#151;and i&#146;m not saying she will be&#151;but&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " if she is where you are then uh&#133;then my feeling weird about it shouldn&#146;t stand in the way.", "answer": " are you sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " yeah. look if-if she&#146;s gonna end up with somebody else, the truth is she couldn&#146;t find a better guy. so&#133;", "answer": " hey thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " so when do you think you&#146;re gonna talk to her?", "answer": " oh my god i have to tell her! i haven&#146;t even thought about what i will say. what should i say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " i&#146;m understanding, but let&#146;s not get carried away.", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, you&#146;re right. what am i gonna say?  oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " &#133;so i&#146;ve been slowly phasing out the wine importing and focusing more on the cheese side of things.", "answer": " cheese you say? that&#146;s some pretty smelly work, huh don?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " excuse me?", "answer": " cheese, it&#146;s smelly. you must smell a lot of the time too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " uh, not really. but when it comes to cheese, i&#146;m one of the people who thinks the smellier the better.", "answer": " me too! yeah, chandler can&#146;t stand it. he won&#146;t even allow me to have blue cheese in the house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " you know what i&#146;d love to do? i would like to go to france and eat nothing but bread and cheese&#151;not even bread, just cheese. no, i want the bread. yeah. ah, and pastries&#133;  and pate. oh, i&#146;m really not high, it&#146;s just i used to be fat.", "answer": " well if you where ever enter the loire valley let me know, i&#146;ve got a great little villa you can stay at.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " is it made of cheese?", "answer": " no. but god, a house made of cheese, wouldn&#146;t that be incredible?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i&#146;d move in tomorrow!", "answer": "  oh come on!  are you listening to this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " i&#146;m so sorry.", "answer": " what do we do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " joey? what&#146;s up?", "answer": " i uh, i just came by because i-i want to talk to you about something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " okay what&#146;s up?", "answer": " here? in the hall? what are we animals?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " well honey, i&#146;m late for a meeting. so can you just make it quick?", "answer": " okay umm, i just came by to tell you that i&#133;want to have dinner with you tonight. that&#146;s all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " i&#146;d like to have don and phoebe over. wouldn&#146;t that be nice?", "answer": " sure, why don&#146;t you set it up. i&#146;ll just be over here, browsing through the personals.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " are you okay? you&#146;ve been acting weird all afternoon.", "answer": " yeah, fine. fine. not perfect!! but good enough.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " jeez! what is with you?", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, did you say cheese?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " all right, what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " phoebe thinks you and don are soul mates, and i don&#146;t believe in that kind of stuff. but then you two totally get along. so look, i won&#146;t stand in your way if you want to run off with don and live in a house of cheese.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " chandler, you don&#146;t believe in soul mates?", "answer": " no. but i&#146;m sure  &#145;tomatoes&#146; does.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i don&#146;t believe in soul mates either.", "answer": " you don&#146;t?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " no. i don&#146;t think that you and i were destined to end up together. i think that we fell in love and work hard at our relationship. some days we work really hard.", "answer": " so you&#133;you don&#146;t want to live with don in a cheese house?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " no, i&#146;ve had second thoughts about that. do you realize how hard that would be to clean?", "answer": " i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " y&#146;know what? i am going to take you out to dinner tonight. i found this place that makes the greatest mozzarella sticks and jalepino poppers .  no? really? they taste so good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " &#133;and i know chandler is kidding but it happens every time he touches my stomach. i mean i&#146;m really worried the baby&#146;s not going to like him.  are you okay?", "answer": " what? yeah! sure! uh, look at the uh, the reason&#133;&#151;is it hot in here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " no. not-not for me, but why don&#146;t you take off your sweater?", "answer": " i would, but this is a nice place and my t-shirt has a picture of calvin doing hobbs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " oh my god! really?! can i see it?", "answer": " yeah. sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " huh. wow, i wouldn&#146;t think hobbs would like that so much.", "answer": " uh&#133; how long have we known each other?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " um, seven&#133;e-e-eight, eight years. wow.", "answer": " uh-huh, long time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " but over the past few weeks&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " hah, sorry about the wait, but it is mega-jammed in here! we have a couple specials tonight&#133;", "answer": " actually uh, could you give us a second?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " so you were saying?", "answer": " i&#146;m not quite sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " okay, well you had asked me how long we had known each other, and i said, &quot;eight years.&quot; and the um, waiter came over and cut his tip in half, and umm&#133;now here we are.", "answer": " yeah, here we are. uhh&#133; i&#133; i think i&#146;m&#133;falling in love with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  what?", "answer": " i&#146;m falling in love with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": "  who are you talking too? oh, you&#146;re kidding! oh, it&#146;s a joke!  it&#146;s funny. it&#146;s funny. i don&#146;t get it.  oh.  okay. umm&#133; i-i&#133;uh, wow. are you uh&#133; how did umm&#133; when?", "answer": " does it really matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " wow! wow. wow. wow, it is hot in here.", "answer": " okay look rach, i know this is a lot. you don&#146;t have to say anything. you-you uh, you take as much time as you need.  okay, you gotta say something!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " joey, joey i love you so much, but i&#133;", "answer": " but.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " joey.", "answer": " yeah-yeah right. that&#146;s okay. that&#146;s fine. that&#146;s uh, pretty much what i was expecting. so uh, it&#146;s no big deal. all right? i think i&#146;m gonna go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " oh joey honey i don&#146;t&#133;i don&#146;t want to lose&#133;", "answer": " hey-hey-hey, hey! you can&#146;t. okay? ever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " i&#146;m so sorry.", "answer": " oh no-no rach, please, don&#146;t be sorry. okay? don&#146;t be sorry.  y&#146;know i was only kidding you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah, that was a real good one.", "answer": " is this your table?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " yeah. waiter no. 2: god, you&#146;re gonna be here all night!", "answer": " i know! i haven&#146;t even read them the specials yet! waiter no. 2: what&#146;s the matter with them?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}]